Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/martzel-baste (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Java

Object-Oriented Programming (OOP)

Visual Basic .NET (VB.NET)

Certifications

Microsoft Technology Associate: Database Administration Fundamentals (MTA)

Microsoft Certified Educator (MCE)

NCII - Hardware Servicing and PC Troubleshooting

Introduction to Programming Using Java

Microsoft Technology Associate: Software Development Fundamentals (MTA)

Honors-Awards

2018 ACM ICPC Philippines Mindanao Invitational Programming Contest - Champion (Coach)

ICPC Philippines Davao Region programming Contest (Second Placer)

2018 ACM ICPC Philippines Mindanao Invitational Programming Contest - 1st Placer (Coach)

Overall Best Presenter

Session Best Presenter

Martzel Baste

Teaching Faculty at Malayan Colleges Mindanao, A Mapúa School Metro Davao

Summary

I have a great passion for teaching, and I have been teaching at several prestigious colleges and universities in the region for more than ten years. I am confident about my skills in Java Programming, Python, VB. Net /C#, Database Programming, Object-oriented Programming, and Data Structures and Algorithm. Currently, I am pursuing my MIT at the University of Immaculate Conception and MIS at the University of Mindanao.

Experience

Mapúa Malayan Colleges Mindanao 4 years 6 months

CCIS Faculty
August 2020 - Present (4 years 5 months)
Davao, Davao Region, Philippines

Teaching Faculty
July 2020 - July 2023 (3 years 1 month)

Jose Maria College of Davao City Teaching Professional June 2022 - July 2023 (1 year 2 months) Philippines

Saint John Paul II College of Davao Teaching Professional August 2020 - May 2023 (2 years 10 months) Davao, Davao Region, Philippines

Alvius Ltd t/a TalentPool
Assistant Project Manager/Junior Data Engineer
November 2019 - August 2020 (10 months)
8th Clapham Park Terrace, Lyham Road, London, United Kingdom,

University of Mindanao
Teaching Professional
April 2012 - August 2020 (8 years 5 months)
Davao del Sur, Davao Region, Philippines

Interface Computer College
Teaching Professional
June 2011 - March 2012 (10 months)
Davao, Davao Region, Philippines

Winwood Group Limited
Business Development Manager
March 2010 - April 2011 (1 year 2 months)

Education

University of Mindanao

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (June 2006 - March 2010)

University of Mindanao

Diploma of Education, Teacher Education and Professional Development,

Specific Subject Areas

University of Mindanao Master's degree, Information Systems

University of the Immaculate Conception Master's degree, Information Technology